export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'When is Harry Potters Birthday?',
        options: ['21 October', '11 June', '31 July', '1 August'], 
        answer: "31 July"
    },
     {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What do Hermione Grangers parents do for a living?',
      options: ['Doctors', 'Dentists' ,'Lecturers', 'Lawyers'], 
      answer: "Dentists"
  
     }, 
     {
     id: 3,
        question: 'Who is the headteacher of Beauxbatons Academy of Magic?',
        options: ['Igor Karkaroff', 'Armando Dippet' ,'Agilbert Fontaine', 'Madame Maxine'], 
        answer: "Madame Maxine"
     },
     {
  
      id: 4,
        question: 'What is the name of Voldemorts snake?',
        options: ['Ningini', 'Nungini', 'Nengani', 'Nagina'], 
        answer: "Nagini"
  
     }, {
  
      id: 5,
      question: 'Where did Vernon Dursley work?',
      options: ['Groundings', 'Grunnings' ,'Grunlings', 'Bank of England'], 
      answer: "Grunnings"
     }, {
  
      id: 6,
        question: 'What is Voldemorts middle name?',
        options: ['Michael', 'Marvin' , 'Maurice', 'Marvolo'], 
        answer: 'Marvolo'
     }, {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What type of dragon was Hagrids pet?',
        options: ['Romanian Longhorn', 'Hungarian Horntail' , 'Peruvian Vipertooth', 'Norwegian Ridgeback'], 
        answer: 'Norwegian Ridgeback'

     }, {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is Madame Hoochs first name?',
        options: ['Rolanda', 'Rowena' , 'Jolande', 'Rowina'], 
        answer: 'Rolanda'

     }, {

        id: 9,
        question: 'What disparaging name is given to people who were born into a wizarding family but who do not have any powers?',
        options: ['Squib', 'Squab' , 'Squeb', 'Squob'], 
        answer: 'Squib'
     }, {

        id: 10,
        question: 'What school was Harry supposed to attend instead of Hogwarts?',
        options: ['Stanwell', 'Stonewall' , 'Ridgewell', 'Stonely'], 
        answer: 'Stonewall'
     }, {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Where was Harry Potter born',
        options: ['Godrics Hollow', 'Geldrics Hallow' , 'Golders Green', 'Galway Grove'], 
        answer: 'Godrics Hollow'

     }, {

        id: 12,
        question: 'Who was the inventor behind the Sorcerers Stone?',
        options: ['Ludo Bagman', 'Celestina Warbeck' , 'Gellert Grindelwald', 'Nicholas Flamel'], 
        answer: 'Nicholas Flamel'
     }, {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What did Nevilles grandmother give in when he was in first year at Hogwarts?',
        options: ['Probity Probe', 'Sneakoscope' , 'Remembrall', 'Revealer'], 
        answer: 'Remembrall'

     }, {

        id: 14,
        question: 'What is the name of Fred and George Wealeys joke shop?',
        options: ['Zonkos Joke Shop', 'Weasley Joke Emporium' , 'Leaping Lizards', 'Wealeys Wizard Wheezes'], 
        answer: 'Weasleys Wizard Wheezes'
     }, {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Who is not a member of the Order of the Phoneix?',
        options: ['Remus Lupin', 'Mad-eye Moody' , 'Cornelius Fudge', 'Severus Snapes'], 
        answer: 'Cornelius Fudge'

     }, {
        id: 16,
        question: 'What model was Harry Potters first broomstick?',
        options: ['Firebolt', 'Cleansweep One' , 'Nimbus 2000', 'Comet Two Ninety'], 
        answer: 'Nimbus 2000'

     }, {
        id: 17,
        question: 'What does the spell Obliviate do?',
        options: ['makes the subject dance', 'deweaponize' , 'unlock doors', 'erases memories'], 
        answer: 'erases memories'

     }
        
       
  ]